<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SE_Project</string>
    <string name="language">en</string>
    <string name="attractions">Attractions</string>

    <string-array name="attraction_1">
        <item name="name">Kordon</item>
        <item name="information">The coastal road, surrounded by cafes, museums and galleries,
            is a popular meeting point to watch the sunset.</item>
        <item name="transportInfo">You can get off at Alsancak by ferry.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attraction_2">
        <item name="name">Kemeralti Bazaar</item>
        <item name="information"> >Kemeralti is a district and bazaar in Izmir, Turkey,
            starting from the Mezarlıkbaşı district in the Konak district and reaching Konak Square,
            where commercial activities are intense. Fevzipaşa Street and
            Eşrefpaşa Street form the land borders of the bazaar.</item>
        <item name="transportInfo">You can get off at Konak by ferry.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attraction_3">
        <item name="name">Izmir Clock Tower</item>
        <item name="information"> Izmir Clock Tower, in Izmir, the Ottoman sultan II. It is a historical
            clock tower built in 1901 to celebrate the 25th anniversary of Abdülhamid\'s accession to the throne.
            It is one of the many clock towers built in the same period in the Ottoman provinces as required by the will of Abdulhamid.</item>
        <item name="transportInfo">You can get off at Konak by ferry.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attraction_4">
        <item name="name">Historical Elevator</item>
        <item name="information"> The Historical Elevator is a historical building located in Izmir.
            It is an elevator tower in Turgut Reis Neighborhood with two elevators operating between
            Mithatpaşa Street, one 58 m higher than the other, and Şehit Nihatbey Street. The elevator,
            which was built by Jewish businessman "Nesim Levi" in 1907, was built to provide fast and easy
            transportation between two districts,from one to the other with 155 steps.</item>
        <item name="transportInfo">You can get off at Karataş stop with Halkapınar-Fahrettin Altay tram.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attraction_5">
        <item name="name">Izmir Archeology and Ethnography Museum</item>
        <item name="information"> İzmir Archeology Museum is a museum where archaeological
            artifacts found in and around İzmir are exhibited. The museum, which was opened to visitors
            in Aya Vukla Church in 1927, has been serving in the modern museum building in Bahribaba Park
            in Konak since 1984. The finds unearthed during excavations in various regions of the Aegean
            Region such as Bayraklı, Ephesus, Bergama, Milet, Klazomenai, Teos and Iasos and shedding
            light on the history of Western Anatolia are exhibited in the museum and in the museum garden.</item>
        <item name="transportInfo">You can reach it by taking the buses numbered 15,27,43,92,152,156 and 887.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attraction_6">
        <item name="name">Izmir Kulturpark</item>
        <item name="information"> Kulturpark is a park located in Izmir, Turkey.</item>
        <item name="transportInfo">You can reach it by taking the bus numbered 63 in Konak</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attraction_7">
        <item name="name">Ephesus Ancient City</item>
        <item name="information"> Ephesus was an ancient Greek city located on the western coast of Anatolia,
            3 km from today\'s Selçuk district, and later an important Roman city.
            It was one of the twelve cities of Ionia during the classical Greek period.
            Its foundation dates back to the Neolithic Age 6000 BC.</item>
        <item name="transportInfo">You can get off at Selçuk Station of the Basmane-Selçuk suburban train.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attraction_8">
        <item name="name">Maritime Museum</item>
        <item name="information"> İzmir Museum Ships or Inciralti Maritime Museum is a maritime museum
            located in İzmir, Turkey. Objects related to the social, historical and economic
            development of maritime are exhibited on three museum ships anchored at Inciralti Pier
            in the town of Balçova. The museum opened to the public on July 1, 2007.</item>
        <item name="transportInfo">You can get off at the Fahrettin Altay metro stop and take the buses numbered 311,480 and 486.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attraction_9">
        <item name="name">Bostanlı Sunset Observation Terrace</item>
        <item name="information"> Standing out with its impressive design,
            the "Bostanlı Sunset Viewing Terrace" offers a wonderful atmosphere where you can lie down against the Gulf view and watch
            the sunset accompanied by the gentle breeze. During your Izmir trip,
            do not forget to see the Bostanlı Sunset View Terrace,
            which promises unforgettable memories.</item>
        <item name="transportInfo">You can reach by ferry, İZBAN or bus.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attraction_10">
        <item name="name">Teos Ancient City</item>
        <item name="information"> Teos, located by the sea one kilometer south of Sığacık Village,
            5 km from Seferihisar District of Izmir, was founded as an Ionian colony in 1000 BC.
            Its founder is known as Athames, the son of Dioysos. Teos first remained under the Persian rule,
            then the Lydians and then again the Persians. With the Ions, Teos gained its independence
            and became an important place in architecture and trade.</item>
        <item name="transportInfo">You can reach Seferihisar by taking the buses numbered 730, 739.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attraction_11">
        <item name="name">Perforated Bay</item>
        <item name="information">It is located in the south of Cesme, 13 kilometers from the center.
            What makes Delikli Bay special is the natural rocks in the sea. The name of the
            bay comes from the cavities of the rocks that emerged as a result of this natural formation.</item>
        <item name="transportInfo">You can walk 4 kilometers to the beach from Alaçalı Port.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attraction_12">
        <item name="name">Cesme Cleopatra Bay</item>
        <item name="information">Cleopatra Bay, one of the hidden coves of Cesme,
            is located within the borders of Alaçatı. The bay,
            which is thought to have taken its name from the fine sands of the beach, is surrounded by rocks.</item>
        <item name="transportInfo">You can reach there by going to Alaçatı Port and taking the road inside Özpamir Sitesi.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attraction_13">
        <item name="name">Altinkum Beach</item>
        <item name="information"> Altinkum Beach is ten minutes away from the center of Cesme.
            The beach is 500 meters long and 15 meters wide. The beach takes its name from its golden sand.
            Sea water is the opposite of other hot spring beaches,
            it is extremely cold even on the hottest days of summer.</item>
        <item name="transportInfo">You can reach there by using Altınkum minibuses in Çeşme</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attraction_14">
        <item name="name">Ege Bilmuh</item>
        <item name="information">Turkey\'s best computer engineering department</item>
        <item name="transportInfo">You can reach it by getting off at the Bornova stop of the metro.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>